babydepot.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy | Burlington

* * *

Our Privacy Policy

Burlington Stores, Inc. respects your privacy and values your trust. This is why we are committed to protecting your privacy and using the information you share with us responsibly to better serve you. Our Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you, as well as why and how we use it to improve your shopping experience with us. 

* * *

Information Collected

We may collect information about you when you visit our stores or website, purchase a product in our stores or online, provide product reviews online, participate in our services, enter our sweepstakes, promotions or loyalty programs, respond to a survey, join our mailing list and receive our marketing material including e-mails. In addition, we collect information from other sources, through or in connection with apps or software sponsored by Burlington Stores, Inc., or on other websites hosted or sponsored by us. We may collect mobile and location-based information if you elect to utilize the Wi-Fi services in our stores. We may combine or cross reference this information with other information that we collect about you to help us improve the quality of your experience with Burlington Stores, Inc. and tailor communications to your interests. The types of information we may collect include your name, postal address, email address, phone number, payment card information, birthday, product preference, demographic information and any other information you choose to provide. We may collect a record of your purchases and any other personal or preference information you provide to us. We may also gather navigational information about where visitors go on our website and partner websites. We can identify you by your IP address and your domain (not by personally identifiable information such as your name, address, or any financial information on your computer). This allows us to see which areas are most visited, how frequently, and for how long. We collect and use this information to improve and optimize your shopping experience with us. 

* * *

Social Media

We invite you and your friends to connect and interact with us using social media. If you are a fan/follower of Burlington Stores, Inc. on social media, you may be sharing certain profile elements, including any comments, with us. Note that you are subject to the terms and conditions and privacy policies of each respective social media platform. 

* * *

Use of Information

Burlington Stores, Inc. may use information about you for various purposes including to process and fulfill your in-store and online orders, to communicate with you and send you information about our products, services, contests, and promotions, to administer and fulfill our contests and promotions, to prevent fraud and monitor against theft, conduct research and help us learn more about your shopping preferences and enhance your shopping experience, and perform other business activities as needed or described elsewhere in this policy. 

Burlington Stores, Inc. only shares information about our customers with affiliated companies, carefully selected vendors, business partners and other organizations to provide better service to you. These companies need information about you to perform their service function (such as to process and fulfill your order, verify your credit card information, and to protect you from fraud). We also share your information with specially chosen companies that help us with marketing functions (such as manage our Internet business, maintain and manage our customer information, as well as market our products and services). And at times we may share information with other companies that have a product or service that we believe will be of interest to you and/or may help them serve you better. We may engage vendors to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may collect certain information from you (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, hardware/software information, cookie ID, IP address, etc.) when you visit our website and use that information to provide advertisements about goods and services that are deemed to be of greater interest to you. 

We may share information about you in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or transfer of all or a portion of our business to another company. In addition, if we are involved in a bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding, such information may be considered an asset of the company, and may be sold or transferred to third parties. 

In certain circumstances, we may share your information in response to legal process or as otherwise required by law. 

* * *

Links to Other Sites

In some areas of our website, we may provide a link to another website. Other websites, including social media sites, have their own policies regarding privacy and security, and these may vary from ours. 

* * *

Updating your Personal Information

You may review, update, correct or delete your online account information at any time by going to "My Account" at the top of any page or by contacting us to request changes to any of your information. 

* * *

Protecting your Information

Log out when you are done on the website to protect yourself against unauthorized access to your account. To log out at any time, click the "Log Out" link. Keep your password safe - do not share it with anyone. 

* * *

Your Rights and Choices

We may use the information we collect to periodically send you emails, mailed circulars or other marketing communications informing you of promotions and offers, or requesting your input. You may opt-out of receiving these communications at any time by changing your preferences on the "Account Information" page in "My Account." If you opt-out, you will still continue to receive order and registry information, answers to customer service questions, and information about changes in our website that might be relevant to you personally. 

You can also ask us to remove your information from our systems or opt out of any third party sharing of your information by contacting us or mail us at Burlington Stores, Inc. ATTN: Customer Relations Department, 2006 Route 130 North, Florence Township, NJ 08518. 

When we send emails to our mailing list, we'll sometimes track when, where and if the email was opened, if any content was clicked on, how long the email was reviewed, on what platform the email was opened (i.e. webmail, desktop, or mobile), the browser used to open the email (i.e. Explorer, Chrome, Firefox, etc.), and who printed and forwarded the emails. We do this to measure the performance of our email campaigns and to improve our offerings to you based on your level of engagement. 

* * *

Children Under 13 Years of Age

It is not our intent to collect personal information about children under the age of 13. A child who is 13 but not yet 18 years of age may use this website only if a parent or legal guardian agrees to be bound by the website's Terms of Use on the child's behalf. Children under 13 years of age may not use this website. 

* * *

Cookies and Other Computer Information

"Cookies" are small text files that are transferred from websites to your computer's hard drive that may serve a variety of purposes (web beacons, Flash cookies and other similar technologies may also be used for these purposes). When you use our website, we, like many other websites, place a cookie on your computer to identify you to provide a more convenient shopping experience and to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our website and third-party sites. If you wish, you can visit our website without cookies by turning them off in your Internet or mobile browser, but then certain features, including adding items to a shopping cart, making a purchase, or using a registry, will not be available. We may use “pixel tags” (e.g. web beacons or similar technologies) that allow us to know if a particular web page was visited, an email opened, links in the email utilized, transactions from online purchases, and whether a particular advertisement or email is effective. To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our and other websites. The information collected does not enable any third-party to identify you individually, without appropriate notice or consent. 

Please keep in mind that Do Not Track is a privacy preference that users can set in some web browsers, allowing opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At this time, the World Web Consortium has not yet established universal standards for recognizable Do Not Track Signals and therefore, Burlington Stores, Inc. does not recognize Do Not Track for all technologies. If and when a standard is set, we may revisit this policy. 

Is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your non-personally identifying browsing interests valuable. However, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. If you configure your browser to reject cookies when you visit these pages, or if you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different device or change web browsers, your opt-out may become ineffective and may need to be repeated. Browser settings, including do not track signals and other mechanisms, will not affect data collection and not constitute an opt-out of advertising-related cookies, personalized third-party advertising or promotional messages from Burlington Stores, Inc.; you must use the opt-out choice described herein in order to opt out from such promotional messages. 

* * *

Security Notice

The security of your personal information is very important to us. In our efforts to protect your online transactions, we use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If your browser is capable of SSL (and most are), your personal information will be automatically encrypted, or encoded, before it is sent over the Internet. 

BurlingtonCoatFactory.com and BabyDepot.com have digital certificates from Verisign, Inc., a well-known provider of Internet trust services. If you enter any protected part of the website where your personal information is needed, a "closed lock" or other icon will appear at the bottom of the page. Site security information can be seen if you click on this icon. This icon alerts you that your personal information is being encrypted when it is transmitted to BurlingtonCoatFactory.com or Baby Depot.com. Additionally, on all protected pages of our website, the address will begin with https://. 

We will never send your credit card information via email.

* * *

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Burlington Stores, Inc. customers who are California residents to request certain information about our disclosure of personal information during the prior calendar year to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please click contact us or mail us at Burlington Stores, Inc. ATTN: Customer Relations Department, 2006 Route 130 North, Florence Township, NJ 08518. California residents under 18 who are registered users may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to this website. To remove posted content or information, please click contact us or mail us at Burlington Stores, Inc. ATTN: Customer Relations Department, 2006 Route 130 North, Florence Township, NJ 08518. Please note that processing your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content that you posted. 

* * *

Notices and Changes

Because our business changes all the time, so does our Privacy Policy and our Security Notice. Please check our website for changes. If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy or our Security Notice, please feel free to contact us. 

* * *

Last Updated: November 2016
